<root>
    <watch>
        <name>chronos</name>
        <description> Mens Watches CHRONOS Top Brand Casual Quartz Military Watches Men Waterproof Date Clock Relogio Masculino Montre Homme Saat. Life  water resistant (Not suitable for swimming, diving, shower etc.). 100% brand new and high quality. Durable leather  band. Precise quartz movement for accurate time keeping. Color may not appear as exactly as in real life due to variations between the computer monitors and naked eye color difference.</description>
    </watch>

    <watch>
        <name>crrju</name>
        <description>1.DURABLE and COMFORTABLE: Rose Gold Six-pin Watch, minutes and seconds chronographs, 12/24 Hours show,Classic 3-Sub Dial Wristwach. Japan quartz movement and battery provide accurate time keeping. Luxury Men's Standard design and comfortable wearing experience, this is a perfect life and travel watch for you.</description>
    </watch>

    <watch>
        <name>megalith</name>
        <description>Luminous Display: Let the dial absorb enough light energy so that the dial will glow in the dark
  Multifunctional Design: Three multifunctional sub-dials support stopwatch and date calendar, Japanese quartz movement and battery provide accurate time keeping 3atm Daily Waterproof: Daily life waterproof, can bear sweat, accidental rain or water splash, but Not suitable for bathing, swimming, diving and so on Stainless Steel Band: Durable and comfortable black stainless steel band fits to daily wear. Band length: Men's standard, Band width: 21mm </description>
    </watch>

    <watch>
        <name>nibosi</name>
        <description>MATERIAL: High quality black stainless steel band with double push button clasp, Precise Japan quartz movement. FUNCTIONS: All sub-dials and watch hands are good working, Full Functional Chronograph, 30M waterproof and Date Display. WATERPROOF: water resistant to 30 meters(99 feet), in general, withstands splashes or brief immersion in water, but not suitable for swimming or bathing</description>
    </watch>

    <watch>
        <name>reloj</name>
        <description>WATCH MOVEMENT: Imported, Japanese Quartz Movement, Provides Precise and Accurate Time. WATCH MATERIAL: Fashion Design Round Dial with Replaceable Multi-Color Striped Nylon Band. Key Scratch Resistance Mineral Watch Glass Mirror, Also Wear Resistant Provides the Comfortable Experience for Everyday Wear. WATERPROOF FOR DAILY USE - 3 ATM Water Resistant, Sweating, Hand Washing, Rain Day, Withstands Splashes or Brief Immersion in Water, NOT Suitable for Diving, Swimming, Snorkeling, Water-related Work. GIFT IDEAS - This Watch Will Come With a Watch Box, High Quality Watches and Exquisite Packaging. As a Best Gift for Birthday, Christmas, Valentine Day, Wedding, New Year, Father's Day, Mother's Day and so on.</description>
    </watch>
    <watch>
        <name>yazole</name>
        <description>100% brand new and high quality. Movement: 68 Movement, Band Material: PU Leather. Case Material: Stainless steel, Display Type: Analog. Case Size: 3.4cm x 3.4cm, Case Thickness: 1cm. Band Length: 24cm</description>
    </watch>
    <watch>
        <name>lige</name>
        <description>Material：Stainless steel case, stainless steel strap comfortable for wearing. Movement：Japanese quartz movement and battery,accurate time keeping for more than 2 years. Multifunction ：All small dial work,three subdials with chronograph minutes/seconds,stopwatch,auto calendar,date display,luminous pointer,water resistant and shock resistant. Waterproof:water resistant to 30 meters(99 feet), in general, withstands splashes or brief immersion in water, can swim.(Please do not operate the button in water).</description>
    </watch>

    <watch>
        <name>fox</name>
        <description>Type : Dress Watch, display Type : Analog, model Number : 057 ,Targeted Group : Women Brand : Miss fox Band Material : AlloyWatch Shape : Round Dial diameter:32mm Thickness of dial:9mm width of band  16mm</description>
    </watch>

    <watch>
        <name>north</name>
        <description>100% brand new and high quality. Display Type: Analog. Band Material: PU Leather. Case Size: 43mm x 43mm. Waterproof: life Waterproof</description>
    </watch>
    <person>
        <name>Herman Samolazov</name>
        <edu>BSTU FIT-2-7</edu>
    </person>>
</root>

